Gustavo Gonzalez Illustrator/Graphic Designer

New York, NY 10030

Email: gustavogonz3393@gmail.com

Tel: 646 416 0199

Professional Profile

Illustrator and Graphic Designer, with more than 4 years of experience in illustration, graphic design, animation, 3D graphics, printed and digital design.

Qualified in all aspects of the design process, from conceptualization to final output.

Offered support creating visual graphics for social media platforms, web design and presentations. Capable of working in a multitude of styles and media, maintening visual coherence for each project Able of working with teams, looking to improve with each proyect.

Skille

Illustration, graphic design, animation, 3D modeling, web design

Work History

2016-2018 Office Manager at UNYPO LLC - New York, New York

Real State Management office

- -Creating and developing brand material for events and events.
- -Provide illustrations and designs for social media.
- -Generate digital and printed graphics for advertising

2015-2016 Graphic Designer at Ardyh Holdings C.A - Caracas, Venezuela

Digital production company in charge of developing campaigns, marketing material and the realization of various events for a variety of clients

- -Conceptualize different aspects for the creation of new brands, from logo design and it's applications, to catalogs that reflect the spirit and message of the brand.
- -Create social media graphics and marketing material to promote our clients brands and have a stronger digital presence in social media.
- -Work with a team of designers, assisting on all aspect for the production of graphics, from retouching and editing photographs to prepare illustrations and graphics to be animated.
- -Work within the paramaters given by the client, offering different solutions to their needs.

2015 Graphic Designer at La Casa Productora - Caracas, Venezuela

Full service digital agency in the area of web design, video production and marketing campaigns.

- -Assist in the design of web sites from a variety of clients, from online stores to make-up artists
- -Create short animations and motion graphics for a variety of videos.
- -Create graphics, illustrations and 3d graphics for client presentations and licitations in order to secure new clients and bussinesses for our company

Education

2018-Present Columbia University Coding Bootcamp

2011-2014 Illustration at Institute of Design of Caracas

Software

Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe After Effects, Cinema 4D, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.JS, Express, MySQL, MONGO, REACT.

Languages

English, Spanish